# LEONARDO IGEL

A front end developer, focused on building front end applications using React.

Highly motivated and happy to learn new technologies and methodologies. Has experience using React, Redux, as well as NodeJS, Express and Mongodb. Looking a front end development positions, where I could contribute and be a pleasant and friendly addition to your team.



## Education

Full stack development course

11/2019 - 03/2020

**Netcraft Academy** 

Learning web development fundamentals, including front end and back end methodologies.

B.A. in Technological Marketing 10/2013 - 10/2016

Sapir Academic College

The studies included courses in business strategies, marketing tools and decision making.

During the studies I learned the basics of HTML5, CSS3 and SQL.



# Work experience

**Chief Security Officer** 02/2019 – 10/2019

Check Point Software Technologies Itd

Maintains safe and secure environment for applicants and employees.

Chief Security Officer

01/2018 - 12/2018

US Embassy in Israel

Maintains safe and secure environment for the embassy and its personnel.

Search Engine Advertising

01/2016 - 01/2017

(PPC) Manager Eschar & more

Monitoring and optimizing PPC campaigns using Google Analytics, Google Adwords, Outbrain and Facebook Ads.

Responsible for direct contact with the clients and making sure their goals are met.

0542518474 leoigeltiko15@gmail.com



## Skills

#### Front End

Javascript (ES6) HTML5 CSS3 React.js Redux Material-UI Bootstrap

#### **Back End**

NodeJS Express MongoDB

#### Marketing

SEO Google Analytics Google Adwords Facebook Ads



## Languages

#### Languages Skills

Portuguese Mother tongue
English Fluent
Hebrew Fluent
Spanish Proficient



## Personal interests

- · Technology and Software development Podcasts.
- Sports and athletics



### Contact







Linkedin

GitH

Portfolio